It's from Kuroi!
There's always a chance
the worst could happen.
Go on ahead, you're faster than me!
Just hurry and catch up to Riko.
I'm sorry, this was my mistake.
Seriously?
I don't think this can
even count as a mistake.
I underestimated how much our
enemies would value Kuroi.
Their next move will probably be
offering to arrange an exchange for her.
Something like trading Amanai for Kuroi.
Or saying they'll kill Kuroi
if we don't kill Amanai.
But we have the leverage in any
negotiation, since we have Amanai.
As long as they set up the location for
the deal, we can make it work out for us.
I'm taking Amanai back to
Jujutsu High immediately.
We can have Shoko or someone
stand in as her body doll.
Hold on!
I'm going to be part of this deal too!
I still can't trust you two yet.
Huh?
You're still saying
that after all of this?
Even if you save her?
Even if you save her, what if Kuroi isn't
back before I assimilate with Tengen?
You mean I haven't?
I haven't even said goodbye to her yet.
The kidnapper will reach
out to us eventually.
But if we realize they're
smarter than we expected,
or it turns out that bringing you will
only lessen Kuroi's chances of survival...
...and we'll have to leave you behind.
Right.
That works.
On the other hand, if you get scared
part way through and want to go home,
we'll just ignore you.
So keep that in mind.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh.
Thank you.
I can't believe I got captured
by the Star Religious Group.
And worse yet, by a non-sorcerer.
I'm just so ashamed of myself.
You couldn't help it if they
caught you off guard like that.
Part of the blame lies with me, too.
Was I really caught off guard?
I thought I was on high alert
after the incident with Q.
Could I?
I still don't have much
recollection of being attacked.
And you all came here by plane?
Were you okay?
You weren't attacked?
Satoru had some good eyes on him.
Before we took off, he checked
over all the passengers and staff.
As well as inside and
outside of the plane.
And while we were in the air, I had
my cursed spirit keep watch outside.
It was safer than traveling by land.
But what I'm curious
about is why they chose
Okinawa as the place to make the exchange.
Probably to buy time, I would assume.
Even if they fail to kill Riko,
they could keep her from making
tomorrow's full moon deadline.
If that were the goal,
they would just choose a rural area
with poor transit infrastructure.
Maybe their plan is to take over
the airport and trap us here.
That's a possibility, but
we're going to be fine.
We're not the only ones here in Okinawa.
Clearly, this mission is far too
difficult for a first-year student.
I'm totally psyched, though.
I can't wait to show off in front of Code.
You know what?
I heard that the
upperclassmen are all worn
to the bone trying to
protect one lone girl.
This is our chance to show
them we've got what it takes.
If a typhoon rolls in and shuts down the
airports, our efforts will be for naught.
It's a sea cucumber!
Gross!
Oh, it's so gross!
Should we really be vacationing like this?
Satoru's the one who suggested it.
He's probably showing consideration
for Riko in his own way.
Though we should all get going.
Satoru, it's time!
Yo, I didn't realize it was that late.
Hmm.
Suguru, let's head back
tomorrow morning instead.
We can't.
The weather's holding steady, right?
Besides, there are fewer curse users
in Okinawa than there are in Tokyo.
Let's keep it a little
more serious, Satoru.
It's better if the time limit on the bounty
runs out while we're mid-flight, right?
Satoru, you haven't released your
technique since yesterday, have you?
You haven't slept either, and you
don't plan to sleep tonight, do you?
Are you sure we don't need
to go back to Jujutsu High?
It's not a problem.
Grinding to endgame in an
MMO is far more training.
And besides, you're here with me too.
Nanami, they said they're
staying another day.
You think something happened?
Thank you.
Very good work, everyone.
We're now inside Jujutsu High's barrier.
Boy, am I relieved to hear that?
Yeah, so am I!
Satoru, hmm?
You really worked hard this time.
I never want to get stuck again
babysitting some kid! Huh?
No, impossible.
We're inside Jujutsu High's barrier.
Excuse me, but have we met before?
Yeah, we have, but don't worry about it.
I'm terrible at remembering
guys' names, too.
On a lark,
I once went to see the
little brat of the Gojo clan,
who'd been born with the Six-Eye.
Never before or after that had anyone
ever noticed me standing behind them,
which is why I wore him down.
Until his senses dulled.
Satoru!
Don't worry, I'm fine.
I didn't make it in time with my
technique, but it missed my vitals.
I then strengthened myself with cursed
energy so the blade couldn't be drawn out.
It felt like nothing more than passing a
safety pin through a big
hole in a knit sweater.
Seriously, I'm fine.
You make sure Amanai is safe.
I'll deal with this guy myself.
Go, Suguru. Take her.
Make sure you two get her to Tengen.
Satoru.
Just be careful.
Follow me!
Right!
Alright, let's get this over with.
That's different from the
blade he stabbed me with.
Where did that cursed spirit come from?
Too many unknowns!
Damn it.
The star plasma vessel is gone.
I had hoped to take you down
with that earlier attack,
but I guess I've lost my edge.
The bounty on Amanai has already
been taken down, you idiot.
I'm the one who took it
down, you arrogant bastard.
When facing people
without openings like you,
you have to first create ups and downs?
leading to several false goals.
I had a good laugh when those star
religious group men went to Okinawa.
It sucked that none of the
sorcerers around her died.
But if I hadn't set that
time limit on the bounty,
then chances are you
wouldn't have released?
your technique until the very end.
Is that stuck?
He's fast, and not just that.
I had a feeling there was
something off about him.
He has zero cursed energy.
He has a heavenly pact,
giving you physical prowess.
I can't imagine anyone who knows
my technique coming without a plan.
Is that cursed tool your
precious trump card?
I hate to disappoint, but
I won't let it get close.
Since he has no cursed energy,
I can't read his presence,
and I can't rely on pure instinct.
There's that cursed
spirit wrapped around him.
I just need to follow its presence.
Even so, he's too damn fast.
Curse Technique
Amplification, Maximum Output!
Blue!
Now there's no cover.
From now on, he can't
launch any surprise attacks.
Did he hide in the woods?
Are those...
fly heads?
Was he keeping them
inside that cursed spirit?
So you're using fly heads to hide.
No, I can't tell where he is.
He's created a blind spot.
I should use blue again.
No, wait, he's after.
Mom and I!
His intuition is keen enough
to sense me empty-handed.
But there's no way his six
eyes would overlook the
unusual cursed energy oozing
from this cursed tool.
However...
That finally got you to focus
on defense with your technique.
A special grace.
A great cursed tool.
Inverted Spear of Heaven.
Its effect is the forced release
of any active techniques.
Well, well.
I think I'm getting my edge back now.
Riko, this is as far as I go.
I wish you luck, Riko. Please be.
Girl, I love you.
I always have, and I always will.
I love you too.
so this is yeah right now we're
in tengens territory this is the
foundation of the nation's key
barriers the main hall of the tombs
of the star once you descend the
stairs pass through the gate and
continue on to the base of the
big tree then you'll be inside the
special barrier which is separate
from the barrier surrounding jujutsu
high only those invited are able
to enter it tengen will protect
you until the assimilation's over
that or we can turn back
around and go home with
Kuroi when our
teacher told us about this mission I
knew there'd be consequences he
said that assimilating would erase
your information that's because
he wanted us to know how serious
a sin we'd commit our teachers
brain may be completely muscle-bound
but he often does roundabout
things before we
even met you satoru
and i had already talked it over
what if the star plasma vessel
kid refuses to assimilate then the
whole thing gets called off sure
about that uh well if you decide
that on your own it might mean you
have to fight Tengen oh what you
scared it'll be fine it'll all work
out somehow.
We're the strongest students
at Jujutsu High School.
So no matter what decision
you make, Satoru and I
will guarantee your future.
Since I was born, I've always known
I was special.
Everyone kept telling me that I was
different, but being special was normal
to me.
And I've lived my life trying to avoid
danger as much as possible for the sake of
this day.
I don't really remember the
day my mother and father died.
I no longer feel
sad or lonely about that.
I figured everything would be
fine, even if I was taken away from
everyone and assimilated.
That no matter how hard that would be,
I would eventually Why do you
stop feeling sad and lonely?
Honestly?
I want to stay with everyone!
I don't want to go!
I'm not ready yet!
I want to travel and have fun!
I want to see and do all kinds of things!
Rico, let's go home.
Oh
Rico
Okay jobs done.
You're free to go now.
Bye
How were you able to get to this place?
How what do you mean? How?
Oh I get what you're asking me!
Satoru Gojo tried stopping
me so I had to kill him.
Is that so?
Die!
They say that it's never too late to
start something new in one's life.
But the bigger problem
is never when to start.
It's always when to quit.
So please look forward to the
next episode, Hidden Inventory 4.
Did I say that right?